http://www.songwriting.net/privacy/

Privacy Statement
USA Songwriting Competition is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our Web site. In order to enhance your experience at our site we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.
What information do we collect? USA Songwriting Competition collects your e-mail address when you sign up for our free e-mail newsletter. We may ask for your name and e-mail address. The more information you share with us (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to enhance and customize your experience on our site.
In addition to the former information, when you enter the USA Songwriting Competition online or by mail, we collect several items of personal information, including your mailing address, telephone number, we do not collect your credit card information once it has been processed. For your security, we never store credit card information on our servers. We transmit credit card information directly to the third party credit card processor through secure connections.
Wherever USA Songwriting Competition collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.
What information do parties other than USA Songwriting Competition collect?Some advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you access or utilize those links. USA Songwriting Competition does not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those advertisers and Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.
What are "cookies" and how do we use them? USA Songwriting Competition uses "Cookies" to track and record your preferences and activity on our Web site. Cookies are small bits of data that are sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. Your cookie may be set at various times during your interaction with our Web site. It is updated from time to time as you access the many different portions of our Web site. Each time you access our site, our server may deliver certain customized information to you based on the data stored in your cookie.
If you do not wish to allow for use of cookies, you can generally opt-out of providing this information by setting your browser to reject cookies. However, please be aware that some areas may not provide you with an acceptable user experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.
What do we do with the information we collect? USA Songwriting Competition 's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Web site. The information we collect (including information contained in your cookie) may be used to provide such capabilities as personalization services, interactive communications, online shopping, and personalized communication between you and the artists you prefer. We may also use the information to estimate the size of our audience and measure certain traffic patterns, to track the progress and number of entries in our promotions and contests, to track visits to and business conducted at our online store, to notify our visitors about updates to our Web site, to contact you for marketing purposes, to contact you on behalf of certain artists and other third parties and deliver targeted advertisements that may be of interest to you. We may occasionally contact you with information regarding special events at USA Songwriting Competition.
In addition, if we feel that a user abuses the USA Songwriting Competition site in any way, we reserve the right to share certain information with third parties. Abuses include (but are not limited to) possible copyright infringement, possible libel and slander, possible credit card fraud.
With whom do we share your information and for what purpose? USA Songwriting Competition does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with others. However, when one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest with the co-sponsor(s). If you do not want your information to be shared, you will be able to choose not to allow the transfer by not using or signing up for that particular service, promotion or contest.
In addition, when you make a purchase through our online store, or sign up to receive promotional items from us, we may share some of your personal information with third parties helping us to complete your transaction or send you the items you signed up to receive. When we share your information with such third parties, we will work to ensure that only the information necessary to complete your transaction is disclosed.
AdRoll.com cookie
AdRoll.com, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on USA Songwriting Competition.AdRoll.com use of the cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of the use of the AdRoll.com cookie by visiting the AdRoll.com and content network privacy policy.
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by USA Songwriting Competition as outlined in this Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others.
Follow Me
Home
Sponsors
Partners
Winners
Press
Testimonials
FAQ
Rules
Blog
Enter Here
Privacy Policy
© 2020 USA Songwriting Competition®. All rights reserved.  The logo of USA Songwriting Competition in Red, white and Blue is a registered trademark..: Visit our Sister Company: IAMA (International Acoustic Music Awards)      Marketing & Promotions
